{
    "id": "b54164e8d68449f0807bf9225595bb62",
    "title": "Allow, Make, Force",
    "exercises": [
        {
            "id": "5f47524ab26e4c4189adfb24796b2724",
            "title": "Make, Allow, Force",
            "questions": [
                {
                    "question": "They ...................................... me repeat the whole story.",
                    "description": "Made is followed by an infinitive without to.",
                    "answers": [
                        "made",
                        "allowed",
                        "forced"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                },
                {
                    "question": "He ..................................... me to leave his home.",
                    "description": "Forced is followed by an infinitive with to.",
                    "answers": [
                        "made",
                        "forced"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                },
                {
                    "question": "I was not ...................................... to meet them.",
                    "description": "Allow is followed by an infinitive with to.",
                    "answers": [
                        "made",
                        "allowed",
                        "forced"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                },
                {
                    "question": "They .......................................... me to give in.",
                    "description": "To force is to compel.",
                    "answers": [
                        "made",
                        "allowed",
                        "forced"
                    ],
                    "correct": 2
                },
                {
                    "question": "You ....................................... to smoke in public places.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "allowed not",
                        "are not allowed",
                        "don't allow"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                },
                {
                    "question": "Will you .................................... me to sit here?",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "force",
                        "allow",
                        "let"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                },
                {
                    "question": "Please ...................................... them go.",
                    "description": "Let is followed by an infinitive without to.",
                    "answers": [
                        "allow",
                        "let",
                        "force"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                },
                {
                    "question": "I was ....................................... to pay for the drinks.",
                    "description": "Either could be used with little difference of meaning.",
                    "answers": [
                        "allowed",
                        "forced",
                        "made"
                    ],
                    "correct": 2
                },
                {
                    "question": "She was ............................................... to apologize to them.",
                    "description": "Either could be used here",
                    "answers": [
                        "made",
                        "allowed",
                        "forced"
                    ],
                    "correct": 2
                },
                {
                    "question": "We do not .......................................... children to stay up late.",
                    "description": "Allow is followed by an infinitive with to.",
                    "answers": [
                        "allow",
                        "let",
                        "make"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                },
                {
                    "question": "He struggled to ........................................ himself understood.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "make",
                        "allow",
                        "force"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                },
                {
                    "question": "I was ………………………….. to visit them whenever I wanted to.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "made",
                        "allowed",
                        "forced"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                }
            ]
        }
    ]
}